# IZUCHUKWU NJOKU

Winnipeg, Manitoba R3T 2K1| 204.230.2253

zuic5527@gmail.com Portfolio: zuicart.github.io/Portfolio

#### CAREER SUMMARY

A Bachelor of Fine Arts Final year student with three years of experience in Digital Art. An
animator experienced in 3-D modeling, rendering, 2-D animation, sound engineering and video editing who
has a passion for various forms of art.

### AREAS OF PROFICIENCY

- Graphic Design
- Adobe Photoshop
- Adobe Illustrator
- Blender (3-D animation software)
- DaVinci Resolve (Professional editing software), Final Cut pro.
- 2-D animation

- Sound Engineering
- Painting and Drawing
- Microsoft Office

### PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

### **GRACE DIGITAL (Part Time),** Winnipeg, Manitoba

**November 2020- Present** 

#### **VIDEO EDITING**

- Created videos with effect and text for audio recording featured on their YouTube Channel.
- Ensuring video and effect is consistent with the message of the brand.

#### **EXPRESS EMPLOYMENT PROFESSIONALS**, Winnipeg, Manitoba August 2018 – November 2020

#### **Contract Staff**

Performed a variety of assigned tasks such as product delivery, product packaging, Moving, Industrial clean up.
 Skilled gained: Attention to details, Ability to learn quickly, Working as a team and independently.

## ANIMATOR AND SOUND ENGINEER (Volunteer), Winnipeg, Manitoba August 2017 – Present

- Created sound content for individuals for use in Rap music.
- Helped designed logos, motion graphic videos and flyers for individuals to promote their brand.
   Skilled gained: Blender, Adobe Illustrator, Sound Engineering, Graphic design, 2-D animation.

### **EDUCATION**

# **Bachelor of Fine Arts (Studio)**

January 2016 - June 2021

University of Manitoba, Winnipeg, Manitoba